Today we're going to be talking about how to buy a new car.
In this segment, we're going to talk about maintaining your new car.
It's really important that you remember that even though you buy a new car, it still has to be maintained.
Every 3000 to 5000 miles you should change your oil.
There is nothing worse than not changing your oil in your new car 'cause it creates sludge.
Sludge in the engine is the only thing that will kill your car.
And remember, at some point your new car will be someone else's used car so the better you take care of your new car, the more money you can get for it when its your used car.
Ask when you buy your car whether or not there is a service contract that's available.
Some manufacturers will offer you for a small amount of money, a contract where they will pay for your normal service, your oil changes, your brake services, your battery problems, things of that nature.
It will be a lot less hassle if you pay for a little bit up front than pay it for it a lot more in the long run.
Keep in mind, even though you have a warranty with your new car, your warranty does not cover your brake pads, your battery, your oil, your windshield wiper blades or any other things that can go wrong with your car that are not covered on the manufacturers warranty.
However, purchasing a service contract throughout the course of your automobile loan can sometimes alleviate some of those little surprises that come up in the future.